[{"answer": "Well, a long time ago, an inventor lived in that mansion. He made many things, I suppose. He also created a man. He gave him inside, a heart, a brain, everything. Well, almost everything. You see, the inventor was very old. He died before he got to finish the man he invented. So the man was left by himself, incomplete and all alone", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Of course, he had a name. His name was my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Did you get a good look", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "She didn't say anything. She rang my doorbell early this morning", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Now you stay in my friend's room tonight. Tomorrow we'll fix your room right", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh, honey, I couldn't have left him there all alone. You would have done the same thing", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Mom, why did you have to bring him in here", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Why does he have to stay here", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Why does he have to stay here", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I do have a little sympathy", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I do have a little sympathy", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Shake his hand", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Shake his hand", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I scared him to death", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Why are you laughing? He got hurt", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "A little shock", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Look, you don't understand, everything he handcuffs or ties will do anything for you", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, no? Why don't you ask him", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "That's not fair", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "There got to be", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend, it's your house. They can't arrest you for setting off your own alarm. We'll just tell them we were breaking in", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "We have to go back", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You are welcome", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I know it was my friend's house", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend, you want to play scissor", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No, why", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Edward-Scissorhands.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes, are you okay", "qsentId": 28}]